[
  {
    "question": "which is the best workout for back",
    "choice1": "dead lift",
    "choice2": "t bar rowing",
    "choice3": "pull ups",
    "choice4": "crunches",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "which is the largest muscle in our body",
    "choice1": "biceps",
    "choice2": "back",
    "choice3": "leg",
    "choice4": "abs",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "who was called as the king of body building",
    "choice1": "phil health",
    "choice2": "dexter jackson",
    "choice3": "kai greene",
    "choice4": "ronnie coleman",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "whey protien is made from",
    "choice1": "chicken",
    "choice2": "milk",
    "choice3": "beef",
    "choice4": "fish",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "gut health is maintained by intake of",
    "choice1": "parotta",
    "choice2": "chilli sauce",
    "choice3": "spinach",
    "choice4": "shavarma",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "how may muscles in triceps",
    "choice1": "2",
    "choice2": "3",
    "choice3": "5",
    "choice4": "1",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "which is most under rated muscle",
    "choice1": "fore arms",
    "choice2": "calves",
    "choice3": "abs",
    "choice4": "hamstring",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "'Feel the pain' was said by",
    "choice1": "davi gogines",
    "choice2": "arnold",
    "choice3": "jay cutler",
    "choice4": "all the above",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "how many hour an average person needs to sleep",
    "choice1": "4",
    "choice2": "6",
    "choice3": "8",
    "choice4": "10",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "king of all muscles",
    "choice1": "back",
    "choice2": "chest",
    "choice3": "leg",
    "choice4": "abs",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "which workout improves the testostrone",
    "choice1": "quads",
    "choice2": "lungs",
    "choice3": "hanging leg rises",
    "choice4": "both a & b",
    "answer": 3
  }


]
